[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "You are, as -- as I said at the top of this show, you are a kind of rock star, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "You know, I never think of it that way, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "What do you call it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "Well, we call it a service.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "Twenty-five minutes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "So you have a 25 minute address which you memorize, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "Do you ever use notes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "Well, I write -- I type what I'm going to say.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "Why have you emerged as the -- the big telegenic superstar do you think of this genre?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", ":", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "You know, I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "What is the state of America spiritually right now, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "Well, I'm an optimist.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 146, "question": "What do you think is the reality?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 147, "answer": "You know, I see it both ways.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "IN", "CD", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", ":", "IN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ":", "IN", "VB", "RB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "Do you feel that America needs to change its direction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "I think in -- in one sense that we do need to change in -- like has been talked about a lot now -- to let go a little bit of the anger.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "Something that's supposed to bring you hope and harmony and peace often has a completely direct affect, doesn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "POS", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "It does.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "Do you try and calm people down?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "RB", "RB", "VB", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 214, "question": "What do you do as a preacher of such influence?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "You know, my encouragement would always be to obviously not use violence, to be peaceful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "-- is the way you speak?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "Exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "Were you allowed to be a naughty boy, Joel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "You know, I didn't -- I never -- I never got off into drugs.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joel?"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "Never tried any of that stuff?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "I never did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "Do you drink?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "I never drank.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "You never drink alcohol?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "Still don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "Never had a drop?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "Never had.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 260, "question": "Not even a tiny, little drop?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "I think, I --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "MD", ":"], "qSentId": 262, "question": "Sneak in the back of the bike shed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "You know, one time we would --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "When your dad wasn't looking, a little drop of cider?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", ",", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "Do you drink?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "You -- you don't smoke?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "Never taken drugs?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "No, don't take drugs.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "You know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "Well, what values did your father instill in you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "I think he instilled in me several.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "Or do you believe that some people are simply born evil?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "Well, when you see someone like Adolf Hitler?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Adolf Hitler"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "Was he born evil do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "You know, I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "Do you -- you feel genuine forgiveness towards him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "You know, I may not right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "Right now, you find it hard to forgive him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "What was the greatest lesson he taught you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "I think the greatest lesson -- well, I think probably the greatest lesson is just to be true to who you are, to follow your own heart.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "Did he ever whack you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "Sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "Do you -- do you -- do you whack your kids?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "We really didn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "Never?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "Maybe a couple times.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "CD", ":"], "qSentId": 470, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "I'm the mean one --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "-- when does that fuse finally go?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "Well, I've really never seen it go.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Victoria"]}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "Isn't that unbelievable?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "Come on, Victoria.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "Isn't that unbelievable?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "He must have a temper.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "Like a fist fight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 513, "question": "Never?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 514, "answer": "Never have.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "Very competitive.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "Guilty?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "We are guilty.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "CD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "How many books have you sold?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "I think I've sold close to 20 million.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "Twenty million books?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "That's all the by product and all that stuff.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "DVDs?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "Well, a lot of those too.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "How many DVDs?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "I don't even know a figure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "Do you know how much you're worth?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "I never dwell on it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 578, "question": "Is it -- is there a contradiction there between saying, you know, \"God wants us all to be rich,\" if actually you're the only rich guy standing there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "EX", "IN", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "``", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "''", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 579, "answer": "Well, again, I don't say that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "But do you want me to be rich?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "I want you to be rich in health, in relationships.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 593, "question": "How much do you think I should have?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "You know, I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 614, "question": "And what would you say, Victoria?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 615, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Victoria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "Could you be happy and poor though, again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "IN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 634, "question": "Do you not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 635, "answer": "I am so --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 642, "question": "Well, let's 20 million books, however many million DVD -- what other income do you have other than those?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "CD", "CD", "NNS", ",", "RB", "JJ", "CD", "NNP", ":", "WP", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 643, "answer": "That's about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 646, "question": "And we're talking like tens of millions of dollars, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 647, "answer": "It's been a lot.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["tens of millions of dollars"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 649, "question": "Do you ever feel guilty?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 650, "answer": "I don't ever feel guilty because it comes from -- it's God's blessings on my life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 657, "question": "And you don't get paid by the church, do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 658, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 667, "question": "You know that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 668, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 669, "question": "You've seen the criticism?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 670, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 679, "question": "-- what is wrong with being a prosperity preacher?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 680, "answer": "Well, that's my whole thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "CC", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 699, "question": "Do you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 700, "answer": "Oh, our church has raised millions and tens and -- you know, I don't even --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 701, "question": "Do -- do you know how much?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 702, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 710, "question": "Have you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 711, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 723, "question": "Which obviously I don't think either of you two were born into great wealth, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "CD", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 724, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 748, "question": "Is homosexuality a sin, in your eyes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 749, "answer": "Yes, I've always believed, Piers, the scripture shows that it's a sin.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 759, "question": "Say, \"Come on, really upset your mother and dad here,\" you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "``", "NNP", "IN", ",", "RB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "RB", ",", "''", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 760, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 773, "question": "The song is on guitar?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 774, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 775, "question": "What do you -- what do you feel when you watch that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 776, "answer": "You know, I'm so proud.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 790, "question": "Which celebrities do you think are good role models?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 791, "answer": "You know --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 797, "question": "Taylor Swift?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 798, "answer": "Yes, she does.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 818, "question": "What is your -- is homosexuality a sin in your eyes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", ":", "VBZ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 819, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 843, "question": "So when you see civil partnerships being sanctioned, you think that's wrong, presumably?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 844, "answer": "Well, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "TO", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 858, "question": "But why are they sinners in your eyes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 859, "answer": "Well, it's strictly back to what the scripture says.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John"]}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "``", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 879, "question": "What would you say to him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 880, "answer": "-- man, I would say \"I love you, Elton John.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "CD", "TO", "NN", "CC", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 894, "question": "Aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 895, "answer": "Well, to me, I just -- I'm not -- I'm not the one to judge and say, you know, who's bad and who's good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 907, "question": "What do you -- how do they change -- what do they have to do to change to be better people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 908, "answer": "Well, I believe it's -- I don't know that I understand it all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 943, "question": "Joel, is it true that you have never had a single date with a woman, or anybody for that matter, until you met Victoria?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 944, "answer": "I had not had a formal date.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joel"], "LOCATION": ["Victoria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 949, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 950, "answer": "I was busy playing sports.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 951, "question": "How old were you when you met Victoria?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 952, "answer": "I was about 22.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 953, "question": "ORGAN: So 22 and never been kissed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", "CD", "CC", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 954, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 960, "question": "Victoria?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 961, "answer": "I had opportunity to break him in right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 962, "question": "Had you -- had you had boyfriends before?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 963, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 969, "question": "So both of -- both of you -- this was the first serious relationship?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "IN", ":", "DT", "IN", "PRP", ":", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 970, "answer": "It was.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 973, "question": "Was it -- was it love at first sight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 974, "answer": "I tell people for me it was.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 991, "question": "I mean, they have to be pretty strict, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 992, "answer": "Well, he wasn't a preacher.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 1002, "question": "That's \"Son of a Preacher Man,\" isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "``", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1003, "answer": "Well, we -- we --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "IN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 1004, "question": "Were you very chivalrous?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 1005, "answer": "I don't know what that means.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 1015, "question": "But are there any annoying aspects to Joel that we should be aware of?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 1016, "answer": "I know there's --", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NN", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 1019, "question": "-- what -- what annoys you about him?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WP", ":", "WP", "NNS", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1020, "answer": "I'm probably way more spontaneous than he is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", ":", "IN", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1033, "question": "Have you been drinking today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1034, "answer": "That was -- that was when I was a lot younger.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 1047, "question": "But when you heard him say that, what was your reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1048, "answer": "I cracked up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 1049, "question": "Did you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1050, "answer": "I thought it was funny.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NNS", ",", "IN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", ":", "VBG", "TO", ":", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 1068, "question": "What's been the single greatest moment of your life outside of marriage and children?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 1069, "answer": "Outside of marriage and children, outside of knowing the Lord -- coming to -- coming to know the Lord.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Compaq Center"]}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 1070, "question": "The -- the moment you'd like to relive again if you had the chance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1071, "answer": "You know, I think it was an amazing moment when we opened up our new facility, the Compaq Center, where we took the church where my parents had had it for 40 years, and we moved into that premier facility there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 1080, "question": "What would your dad have made of that you think at the moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1081, "answer": "He would be proud.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RBR", "."], "qSentId": 1101, "question": "Will you feel the same way about meeting me, do you think, Joel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 1102, "answer": "I do even better.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joel?"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 1110, "question": "Madonna or Lady Gaga?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 1111, "answer": "Lady Gaga.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 1129, "question": "How on Earth have you connected to Lady Gaga?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 1130, "answer": "Oh, not --", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Earth"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1137, "question": "Simon Cowell -- angel or the devil?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ":", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1138, "answer": "Oh, I think he's an angel.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1141, "question": "What?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 1142, "answer": "I think -- I think he's -- I think he's smart.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 1143, "question": "You both think he's an angel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "DT", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1144, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 1152, "question": "Justin Bieber, cute or annoying?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "CC", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 1153, "answer": "Oh, I --", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Justin Bieber"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 1164, "question": "Is the death penalty ever justified, and if so, when?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "VBN", ",", "CC", "IN", "RB", ",", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 1165, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Osama Bin Laden"]}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 1167, "question": "I struggle with that, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 1168, "answer": "If Osama Bin Laden was captured tomorrow --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 1170, "question": "-- should he be executed?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 1171, "answer": "I think that it would probably be a good idea, you know, because of the people they hurt.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 1172, "question": "So execute him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1173, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 1174, "question": "Did Michael Vick deserve his second chance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1175, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Vick"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 1176, "question": "Do you think everybody does?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 1177, "answer": "I think everybody does.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]